http://www.stmaryscambridge.co.uk/terms-of-use.htm

Our Magnolia tree
Original log book (1901-27)
Design Technology
English as an Additional Language (EAL)
Home>Terms of use
Your access to this website is subject to legally binding terms and conditions.
Carefully read all of the following terms and conditions. Accessing this website is the equivalent of your signature and indicates your acceptance of these terms and conditions and that you intend to be legally bound by them. If you do not agree with these terms and conditions, please leave the site immediately.
This is an agreement between you ("you”) and St Mary’s School, Cambridge (the “School”). “We” and “Us” means both You and the School. The effective date of this Agreement is when You accept this Agreement in accordance with the procedure set out above.
You hereby consent to the exchange of information and documents between Us electronically over the Internet or by e-mail, and that this electronic Agreement shall be the equivalent of a written paper agreement between Us.
1. Ownership and copyright
You acknowledge that any and all information, content, reports, data, databases, graphics, interfaces, web pages, text, files, software, product names, School names, trade-marks, logos and trade names contained on this web site (collectively the “Content” including the manner in which the Content is presented or appears and all information relating there to, are the property of their respective owners as indicated, the School or its licensors.
2. Permitted use
The School hereby grants to You a personal, non-transferable and non-exclusive license to access, read and download one copy of the Content.
3. Restrictions on use
You agree that You will not:
(i) distribute the Content for any purpose including without limitation compiling an internal database, redistributing or reproduction of the Content by the press or media or through any commercial network, cable or satellite system; or
(ii) Create derivative works of, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, adapt, translate, transmit, arrange, modify, copy, bundle, sell, sub-license, export, merge, transfer, adapt, loan, rent, lease, assign, share, outsource, host, publish, make available to any person or otherwise use, either directly or indirectly, the Content in whole or in part, in any form or by any means whatsoever, be they physical, electronic or otherwise. You shall not permit, allow or do anything that would infringe or otherwise prejudice the proprietary right of the School or its licensors or allow any third-party to access the Content. The restrictions set out in this Agreement shall not apply to the limited extent the restrictions are prohibited by applicable law.
4. License to use your information
With the exception of personal information, You hereby grant to the School the perpetual, unlimited, royalty-free, worldwide, nonexclusive, irrevocable, transferable license to run, display, copy, reproduce, publish, bundle, distribute, market, create derivative works of, adapt, translate, transmit, arrange, modify, sub-license, export, merge, transfer, loan, rent, lease, assign, share, outsource, host, make available to any person or otherwise use, any information or other content You provide on or through this web site or which is sent to the School by e-mail or other correspondence, including without limitation, any ideas, concepts, inventions, know-how, techniques or any intellectual property contained therein, for any purpose whatsoever. The School shall not be subject to any obligations of confidentiality regarding any such information unless specifically agreed by the School in writing or required by law. You represent and warrant that you have the right to grant the license set out above.
5. Personal information
The School may from time to time, but is not obligated to, monitor your use of the website and collect, store and use personal information about You for providing service you may of requested and You hereby consent to such collection, storage, use and disclosure and waive any right of privacy You may have. You may access, correct and delete your own personal information stored by school by contacting us in writing.
6. Limitations on liability and disclaimers
There is no guarantee that personal information and transactions on this website or on the internet will be maintained confidential and secure. The use of this website and the content is at your own risk and the School assumes no liability or responsibility pertaining to the content, your use of the website or the receipt, storage, transmission or other use of your personal information.
This website and its content are not to be construed as a form of promotion. This website may contain links to other sites. The School does not assume responsibility for the accuracy or appropriateness of the information, data, opinions, advice, or statements contained at such sites, and when you access such sites, you are doing so at your own risk. In providing links to the other sites, the school is in no way acting as a publisher or disseminator of the material contained on those other sites and does not seek to monitor or control such sites. A link to another site should not be construed to mean that the school is affiliated or associated with it.
The school does not recommend or endorse any of the content, including without limitation any hyperlinks to or content found, on other website. The mention of another party or its product or service on this website should not be construed as an endorsement of that party or its product or service. The school will not be responsible for any damages you or any third-party may suffer as a result of the transmission, storage or receipt of confidential or proprietary information that you make or that you expressly or implicitly authorise the school to make, or for any errors or any changes made to any transmitted, stored or received information. You are solely responsible for the retrieval and use of the content. You should apply your own judgement in making any use of any content, including, without limitation, the use of the information as the basis for any conclusions.
The content may not be accurate, up to date, complete or un-tampered, and is not to be relied upon. The content is provided for educational and informational purposes only and should not be interpreted as a recommendation for any specific product or service, use or course of action. The content on this website is not intended to be used as a substitute of any kind for professional advice. It is your duty to obtain professional advice from a qualified professional advisor to meet your needs. You should not act or rely on any of the content without seeking advice of a qualified professional.
Except as expressly provided in this agreement, this website and all content, products, services and software on this website or made available through this website are provided “as is” without any representations, warranties, guarantees or conditions, of any kind, whether express or implied, statutory or otherwise, including but not limited to, warranties as to uninterrupted or error free operation, availability, accuracy, completeness, currentness, reliability, timeliness, legality, suitability, privacy, security, merchantability, quality, title, non-infringement or fitness for a particular purpose, or those arising out of a course of dealing or usage of trade. In no event will the school, its affiliates, agents, licensors, suppliers, or their respective directors or employees be liable for any special, indirect, incidental, punitive, exemplary, aggravated, economic or consequential damages, howsoever caused, including but not limited to: damages for loss of use, lost profits.
Even if the school or any of its lawful agents or employees have been advised of the possibility of such damages or claim. In no event will school, its affiliates, agents, licensors, suppliers, or their respective directors or employees, be liable for damages or losses resulting from: viruses, data corruption, failed messages, transmission errors or problems; telecommunications service providers; links to third-party websites; the internet backbone; personal injury; third-party content, products or services; damages or losses caused by you, or your respective employees, agents or subcontractors; loss of use or lack of availability of facilities including computer resources, routers and stored data; the use or inability to use this web site or the content; any other web site accessed to or from this web site; or events beyond the reasonable control of the school, even if the school or any of its lawful agents, or employees have been advised of the possibility of such damages or claim. In no case will the school’s, its affiliates’, agents’, licensors’, suppliers’, and their respective directors’ and employees’ cumulative total liability arising under any cause whatsoever (including without limitation breach of contract, tort, negligence, gross negligence, or otherwise) be for more than the amount, if any, paid by you under this agreement to access this website, in the year in which the claim arose.
The school assumes no obligation to update the content on this site. The content on this site may be changed without notice to you. The school is not responsible for any content or information that you may find undesirable or objectionable. The school disclaims any liability for unauthorised use or reproduction of any portion of the website. Accessing the content from territories where it may be illegal is prohibited.
7. Termination
This Agreement is effective until terminated by the School, with or without cause, in the School’s sole and unfettered discretion. The School may terminate this Agreement without notice to You if You fail to comply with any of its terms. Any such termination by the School shall be in addition to and without prejudice to such rights and remedies as may be available to the School, including injunction and other equitable remedies. The disclaimers, limitations on liability, ownership, termination, interpretation, Your license to the School, Your warranty and the indemnity provisions of this Agreement shall survive the termination or expiry of this Agreement.
Request a prospectus
This website and services embedded within it use cookies to offer you the best user and functional experience and to provide us with performance statistics. Please click more information to read about cookies and to view the cookies we use.
More information |
Block cookies |
Privacy notices
If you choose to block cookies some parts of this website may not operate. To block cookies please do this within your browser settings. Most browsers allow you to block cookies within their settings and we have provided links to the most commonly used browsers.
Please view our cookie details page for more information on the cookies we use.
